{
  "name": "Harry Potter Trivia",
  "author": "github.com/whitespace404",
  "length of the longest question": "...",
  "length of the longest option": "...",
  "questions": {
    "questions-ps": [
      {
        "question": "In Harry's first Potion's class, they learn how to make a potion that would ____.",
        "options": [
          "put the drinker into dreamless sleep",
          "make the drinker sneeze profusely",
          "cure boils"
        ],
        "answer": "cure boils",
        "option": "c",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "On Dumbledore's left knee, you can find a scar shaped like ____.",
        "options": [
          "the floor plan of the Ministry of Magic",
          "a lightning bolt",
          "the map of the London Underground"
        ],
        "answer": "the map of the London Underground",
        "option": "c",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],

    "questions-cs": [
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "a",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "b",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],
    "questions-pa": [
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "a",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "b",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],

    "questions-gf": [
      {
        "question": "What month and day is assigned to the first task?",
        "options": ["September 14", "November 24", "September 24"],
        "answer": "November 24",
        "option": "b",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "Who put up half their shares on their eel farm for a week long Quidditch world cup match in a bet with Ludo Bagman?",
        "options": ["Edmund Gaddlegate", "Agatha Timms", "Gawain Robards"],
        "answer": "Agatha Timms",
        "option": "b",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],
    "questions-op": [
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "a",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "b",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],

    "questions-hbp": [
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "a",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "b",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ],

    "questions-dh": [
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "a",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "q",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
        "answer": "b",
        "option": "a",
        "comment": ""
      }
    ]
  }
}
